Pradnesh **Shinde**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER · MEAN STACK DEVELOPER

6, Kulswamini, Raj-rajeshwari, Sai-lani baba, Jail Road, Nashik Road, Nashik - 422101

□ (+91) 9822908867 | ☑ pradshinde101@gmail.com | ☑ PradneshShinde | ☐ pradnesh-shinde-64560958 | ⑤ pradneshshinde

"Walking on water and developing a software from specifications are easy if both are frozen."

Summary_

4+ years of experience working as a font-End Web developer. Strong technical skills in complex website development including web-based applications. Experience developing the **Single Page Applications using Angular**. Experience in back-end development using **Node.Js** with database exposure of **MySQL**. Having the good experience and knowledge of latest **Javascript** concepts. Constant learner for new solutions to the problems and task, keeping touch to the new arrivals in technology

Ski**lls**

Web Technologies HTML4/ HTML5, CSS3, ¡Query, Bootstrap, Angular 4+, Node.js, React.js, Ajax, JSON, Angular CLI

Programming Languages TypeScript, JavaScript,

Frameworks ExpressJs

Servers IIS.

Version Controls Git

IDE's Visual Studio code

Database My SQL

OS Windows

Languages English, Marathi, Hindi

Work Experience

WINJIT TECHNOLOGIES PVT. LTD.

Nashik, Maharashtra, India

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & MEAN STACK DEVELOPER

July. 2017 - PRESENT

- $\bullet \ \ \text{Designed and developed front-end website for 3+ websites, using Angular\ , with back-end as NodeJS}$
- Designed and developed the application using Angular 4,5 framework along with HTML5, CSS3, Type Script, Java Script, Bootstrap, Node.js, NPM.Mv SOI
- Worked Extensively with Angular CLI for creating components, Services, pipes, Directives.
- Worked on many features of Angular 4,5 like new if else syntax, ng-templates, form validators, Subject-Behavior, Auth-Guards etc.
- Experienced with deployments, maintenance of application on IIS Server

DATAMATICS GLOBAL SERVICES LTD.

Nashik, Maharashtra,India

April. 2016 - July. 2017

Was indulged in Sharepoint technology

- Experience in Asp.Net Technology.
- Worked in developing and maintaining the website in Asp.Net and Sharepoint.

Education_

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CDAC Pune, Maharashtra, India.

SUNBEAM INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

August 2015 - February 2016

Score : B+

Engineering in Electronics & Telecommunications

Nashik, Maharashtra, India.

MET INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING

June 2010 - June 2014

• Score: 64.93 %

Diploma in Electronics & Telecommunications

Nashik, Maharashtra, India.

K.K.WAGH POLYTECHNICS

June 2007 - June 2010

• Score: 82.48 %

JUNE 18, 2020 Pradnesh S Shinde · Resume

Project Handled

TCBS - Transaction Capital Business Solutions (South Africa)

https://tcbusiness.co.za/ Duration: 7 Months

ANGULAR DEVELOPER · Team Size: 2

- Worked as **Front-End** developer
- Responsible for developing website in **Angular4** version
- · As and when required took the role for developing the api in ASP.NET MVC as Back-End developer

Fullerton- Self Employed Professional- Online Lending Platform

www.fullertonindia.com/index.aspx

Duration: 5 Months

Angular Developer · Team Size: 3

- · Worked as Front-End developer
- Responsible for developing website in **Angular5** version
- Integration of JAVA Api's in the application
- · Worked in creating the custom pipes for the application, also use of the angular concepts to its best.

Morpheus. Network - Blockchain Powered Global Supply (Canada)

https://morpheus.network/

Duration: March 2018 - Till Present

MEAN STACK DEVELOPER

- · Team Size: 4
- · Worked as Mean Stack developer
- Responsible for developing website in **Angular5** version
- Responsible for developing API's in **NodeJS** using **ExpressJS** as a framework
- Responsible for both front-end and back-end task for the assigned module
- · Work hand in hand with client directly, responsible for direct client interaction for the task discussion of the modules, for providing better solution to their requirement.
- Opportunity to develop the **Ethereum's Private Side-Chain** for the project
- · Integration of different 3rd party services as when required in Project (Access-Pay, Simply-Duty, EasyPost, Twillio, MapQuest
- Worked on pdf-generation using 3rd party NPM html-pdf (Back-End)

Honors & Awards.

PROFESSIONAL

2018 Best Project, Morpheus. Network in Winjit One World (WoW) Nashik,India

2019 Best Team, Morpheus. Network Nashik,India

DOMESTIC

2008 1st Place, Swimming Competition Organised By Mayor's Club Nashik,India